Today Tufts UP057
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Today Tufts
1977 -- 1978
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office for Campus Life
UP057
1.25 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issue of Today Tufts. It was the predecessor to the Tufts Daily,and was a student-run newspaper of Tufts University. Today Tufts began on September 20, 1977 and ceased publication in 1979. Each volume covers one academic year. The issues are undated and have been dated by the archives staff. The archives holds one copy of each Today Tufts issue.
Related Materials
UP029, The Tufts Daily, DCA
Biographical / Historical
Responsibility for new student orientation once fell under the pervue of the Orientation Committee. Currently, the Office for Campus Life takes a leadership role in the planning and implementation of New Student Orientation.
- Today Tufts, 1977 -- 1978; UP057.001; 1.25 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of Today Tufts, the predecessor to the Tufts Daily. It was a student-run newspaper of Tufts University. Today Tufts began on September 20, 1977 and ceased publication in 1979.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 20, 1977; UP057.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 21, 1977; UP057.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 23, 1977; UP057.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 26, 1977; UP057.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 27, 1977; UP057.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 28, 1977; UP057.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 30, 1977; UP057.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 3, 1977; UP057.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 5, 1977; UP057.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 6, 1977; UP057.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 7, 1977; UP057.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 11, 1977; UP057.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Today, Oct. 12, 1977; UP057.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Today, Oct. 13, 1977; UP057.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 14, 1977; UP057.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 17, 1977; UP057.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 18, 1977; UP057.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 19, 1977; UP057.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 21, 1977; UP057.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 24, 1977; UP057.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 25, 1977; UP057.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 26, 1977; UP057.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 27, 1977; UP057.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 1, 1977; UP057.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 2, 1977; UP057.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 3, 1977; UP057.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov 4, 1977; UP057.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 7, 1977; UP057.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 8, 1977; UP057.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 9, 1977; UP057.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 10, 1977; UP057.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 11, 1977; UP057.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 14, 1977; UP057.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 15, 1977; UP057.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 16, 1977; UP057.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 17, 1977; UP057.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 18, 1977; UP057.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 22, 1977; UP057.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 29, 1977; UP057.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 30, 1977; UP057.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Dec. 1, 1977; UP057.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Dec. 2, 1977; UP057.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Dec. 5, 1977; UP057.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Dec. 6, 1977; UP057.001.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Dec. 7, 1977; UP057.001.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Dec. 8, 1977; UP057.001.001.00046 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Dec. 9, 1977; UP057.001.001.00047 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Dec. 12, 1977; UP057.001.001.00048 (Box 1)
  - Today Tufts, Dec. 13, 1977; UP057.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Dec. 14, 1977; UP057.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Jan. 23, 1978; UP057.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Jan. 24, 1978; UP057.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Jan. 25, 1978; UP057.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Jan. 26, 1978; UP057.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Jan. 27, 1978; UP057.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Jan. 30, 1978; UP057.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Jan. 21, 1978; UP057.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Feb. 1, 1978; UP057.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Feb. 2, 1978; UP057.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Feb. 3, 1978; UP057.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Feb. 6, 1978; UP057.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Feb. 7, 1978; UP057.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Feb. 8, 1978; UP057.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Feb. 9, 1978; UP057.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Feb. 13, 1978; UP057.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Feb. 15, 1978; UP057.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Feb. 17, 1978; UP057.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Feb. 21, 1978; UP057.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Feb. 22, 1978; UP057.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Feb. 23, 1978; UP057.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Feb. 24, 1978; UP057.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Feb 27, 1978; UP057.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, March 1, 1978; UP057.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, March 2, 1978; UP057.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, March 9, 1978; UP057.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, March 22, 1978; UP057.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, March 23, 1978; UP057.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, March 24, 1978; UP057.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Apr. 5, 1978; UP057.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Apr. 11, 1978; UP057.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Apr. 17, 1978; UP057.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Apr. 19, 1978; UP057.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Apr. 21, 1978; UP057.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Apr. 25, 1978; UP057.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Apr. 26, 1978; UP057.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, May 1, 1978; UP057.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, May 2, 1978; UP057.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 12, 1978; UP057.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 14, 1978; UP057.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 15, 1978; UP057.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 18, 1978; UP057.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 19, 1978; UP057.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 20, 1978; UP057.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 21, 1978; UP057.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 22, 1978; UP057.001.002.00047 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 25, 1978; UP057.001.002.00048 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 26, 1978; UP057.001.002.00049 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 27, 1978; UP057.001.002.00050 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 28, 1978; UP057.001.002.00051 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Sept. 29, 1978; UP057.001.002.00052 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 2, 1978; UP057.001.002.00053 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 3, 1978; UP057.001.002.00054 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 4, 1978; UP057.001.002.00055 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 5, 1978; UP057.001.002.00056 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 6, 1978; UP057.001.002.00057 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct 10, 1978; UP057.001.002.00058 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 11, 1978; UP057.001.002.00059 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 12, 1978; UP057.001.002.00060 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct 13, 1978; UP057.001.002.00061 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 16, 1978; UP057.001.002.00062 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 17, 1978; UP057.001.002.00063 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct 18, 1978; UP057.001.002.00064 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 19, 1978; UP057.001.002.00065 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct. 20, 1978; UP057.001.002.00066 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct 23, 1978; UP057.001.002.00067 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct 24, 1978; UP057.001.002.00068 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct 25., 1978; UP057.001.002.00069 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct 26, 1978; UP057.001.002.00070 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct 27, 1978; UP057.001.002.00071 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Oct 30, 1978; UP057.001.002.00072 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 1, 1978; UP057.001.002.00073 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 2, 1978; UP057.001.002.00074 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 6, 1978; UP057.001.002.00075 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 7, 1978; UP057.001.002.00076 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 8, 1978; UP057.001.002.00077 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 13, 1978; UP057.001.002.00078 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 17, 1978; UP057.001.002.00079 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 20, 1978; UP057.001.002.00080 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, November 21, 1978; UP057.001.002.00081 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 22, 1978; UP057.001.002.00082 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 28, 1978; UP057.001.002.00083 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Nov. 29, 1978; UP057.001.002.00084 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Dec. 1, 1978; UP057.001.002.00085 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Dec. 4, 1978; UP057.001.002.00086 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Dec. 5, 1978; UP057.001.002.00087 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, March 30, 1978; UP057.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Today Tufts, March 31, 1978; UP057.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Today Tufts, April 3, 1978; UP057.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Today Tufts, April 4, 1978; UP057.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Today Tufts, April 12, 1978; UP057.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Today Tufts, April 13, 1978; UP057.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Today Tufts, April 14, 1978; UP057.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Today Tufts, April 20, 1978; UP057.001.003.00008 (Box 3)